[Music]
welcome to yet another skincare product
video that I am so excited to be talking
about and reviewing when I tell you that
I am on Cloud9 I am so ecstatic I am so
happy to be reviewing this product I
keep looking that side because as I look
this side I can see it and I'm
love the name of the product is called
Le by Amanda duond it's a proudly South
African product well am is from isand
but umland isini in South Africa it's
the same thing right we siblings we
siblings but it's a probably South
African product anyway um I just want to
say I really was a bit skeptical when it
comes to my face and try new products I
really need to think twice do I really
want to do this do I really want to try
this product out and I'm so glad that I
tried the product out and I'm so glad
that I gave myself some time a few weeks
to use it so that I can come up on here
and give you a proper and far um review
and I'm loving the results on my skin
without wasting any more time let's jump
right into it let me grab the box and
show you
guys so this is the Box this is the
smallest box that they have and it comes
out with every everything from the
cleanser from the
cleanser to the what is this again this
is the finished spray that you use after
putting on makeup that you can also put
it on after you can also apply it on on
your face spray it on your face after
applying all the products or in between
the products it will depend on what you
prefer and what you want so let me come
closer let me show you so this is the
cleanser
can you guys see I hope you guys can see
the lighting is just so bright on my
eyes this is the cleanser right and this
is the
serum this is the serum and this is um
the
moisturizer and this is a moist a
moisturizer that also has SPF in it and
this is a uh a setting spray this is a
setting spray let me try make sure that
you guys see oh my God if you guys can
really see I will take um a picture and
just put
it here yes okay moment of silence for a
picture that will be up here anyway um
so it retails for
549 rent so I bought this at fosini so
you can get it at any fosini wherever
you are in South Africa I bought mine at
fusini fi at for Mall in jber yes um so
let me just show you so I've already
used this so don't be surprised when you
see that product are already used like I
said I gave myself an opportunity to use
the products for like a few weeks I
think it's been 3 weeks and the results
were so
quick um things have even moved around
anyway here's the cleanser
let me make sure that it um sorry guys
can you see it has the here's the
cleanser I will also put I'll be putting
pictures on the site as well here's the
cleanser it is 50 mil it is 50 mil it's
quite small when I was buying these
products actually they were like this is
the smallest box that they have this is
for when you want to try the product on
your face before you buy big big big big
in big bottles you know so yeah and this
is the
serum this is the
serum this is the serum and it's just 10
mil guys 10 mil it finishes so quickly
it's so tiny so
cute and this is the
moisturizer creamy Del cream that's what
it's called see I've been been using it
so in 3 weeks already these products are
finished they are done the serum is done
done done the serum is finished I can
tell you that um and this is
um um another moisturizer that has um
SPF for all all the shade this is it I
don't really use much of it I didn't
really use much of it because I'm
reviewing and I'm going to be honest out
of all the products I honestly don't
really like this so I used it a few
times and I put it away way maybe I'll
give it to a friend or something I I I
don't really like it so I'm using a
different
SPF for my
face and then here's the setting spray
leave has the setting
spray the setting spray is 30 mil so
it's literally just small small small
small um bottles just to sample on your
face here they are looking fabulous I
love the packaging don't you so like I
said um the spray the setting spray you
can spray it in between um putting on
your products on your face or right
after applying all your products just
for your face to feel
hydrated and
then because um the samples did the
things they did the things on my face
and I'm happy and I was like you know
what I'm just going to continue using L
I went on and
bought big bottles big containers I hope
you guys can
see but like I said I will put a picture
up in here so in this product I mean in
this box um you only get the cleanser as
you can see you only get the cleanser
you only get the serum and you get the
moisturizer
and this thing what's it called Le leave
Che brawler gold key ask me what this is
for and I will tell you lies I don't
know what this is I'm so super excited
that I will be unboxing this with you
guys this is sealed I have not opened it
so I will be opening it with you guys
and this retails for much does this
retail for okay I don't know why there's
no price here but it retails for
something so if you are rounding it off
all of these three products are 900
bucks how affordable is that how
affordable is that it really is
Affordable if you a skincare gily you
know what I'm talking about this is
Affordable compared to other skin care
products now let's open up and
see hey I'm doing it with you
guys okay
I just getting stuck as I open so this
is how the Box looks like this is how
the Box looks like let's see I just want
to see how to open it so that things
don't fall cuz I would
cry so let's open okay okay let me try
can you guys see yeah I don't want to do
it on my own hope you
guys I don't know if I'm doing this the
right way guys okay let me open it off
camera guys I I can't do this with you
guys let me just give me 3 seconds and
I'll be back I am so embarrassed guys I
just yeah I just messed up but it's okay
I had to do something I had to come up
with a plan to open this box anyway yeah
it looks messy but anyway here are the
products here are the products look at
how big this cleanser is compared to the
other one so this cleanser is um 200 mil
this cleanser is 200 mil it is so
big it is so big now let's go through
the ingredients so that this cleanser
contains um Roy boss and
cus salicylic salicylic acid yes it's
salicylic acid and ninite ninite I know
how to pronounce it properly because
this is a product that um I know my skin
needs so I had to learn how to pronounce
it properly so this one it's Sal
salicylic yes salicylic acid it's
salicylic acid now nide I know exactly
what it works for
nide um helps with if you are struggling
from hyperpigmentation and dark
marks nide is your girl nide is your
girl so if you want to even out your
skin look for a product that has nce it
but now we reviewing Le so please go by
Le this product Oh I love it so yeah I
don't know if you guys will be able to
see what it contains if you guys can
read there um rayar salicylic AET and
nce cite and it's 200
mil this is how the bottle looks like um
so let's compare it with the smaller
bottle to show you that this is just a
simple and this is when you actually are
sure that you want to continue using
these products so look the difference
this cannot even fit in frame let me go
backwards can you guys see the
difference so like I said this is 200
mil and this
is um 50 mil and here is the
serum
Lea the serum now has vitamin C hyaluron
and turmeric or
turmeric let me show it to you guys I
hope you guys can see I hope it's um
focusing cuz I can't see so we all know
what vitamin c does we all know what
hyaluronic acid does if you don't know
what hyaluronic does is hyaluronic is
very good for people with dry faces
because it highres the face it really
hydrates the face like that and you can
feel it as well and vitamin C obviously
brightens you know brightens up your
face um evens out your face as well just
like
nicomide um and then turmeric does the
same thing almost the same thing as what
T um vitamin C is doing and what
Nite does so I'm in love what's
up now let's
compare so this is the small bottle and
this the small bottle container and this
is the big container container and the
big container is 30 mil the small
container is 10 mil I love love love
love this ser and now the
moisturizer here is the
moisturizer um so the moisturizer let me
let me show you the moisturizer before I
read out the what it has what it
contains the ingredients baby so it has
it contains peptides peptides Rose T and
African
mahogany yep let's compare with a small
one like literally this is just a sample
as you can see so this one is 50 mil and
the sample is 15 meal now I honestly
don't know what
peptides um helps with African mahogany
rose hip I'm not sure um I don't know if
I should Google and read it out for you
guys or I'll run I'll just write what
peptides is as I'm speaking right now I
should have a caption um explaining what
peptides does to the Face rose hip what
rose hip does I forget how he does I
know I remember I don't it's just that I
don't remember but I did obviously
Google so when I'm in a shop and I'm
about to buy a new skincare product I
whip out my phone and if I see any
ingredient that I do not know what it
means I will Google it and I and if I
feel that okay this is what I need for
my face then I will take it so for me to
have taken this it means that it does
the things but the will be a caption
that explains what peptides and rose hip
and African mahogany really does to the
face and oh I have an extremely dry face
and what I love about these products
they are for all skin skin care um no
they are for all skin types and I
promise you I'm not lying to you guys
any product I'm very skeptical about a
product that says um it is it Cates for
all skin care I don't do that I always
always always always make sure that I go
for um products that are specifically
for dry skin but with these products I
trusted them the Holy Spirit led me to
this to these products honestly the Holy
Spirit was like my child my girl my
daughter I'm telling you is the way to
go so they are for for all skin care
types let me show you
M yes see here fulls siiz product for
all skin types normally I would go for
for for for dry skin it should be
written for dry skin but this one is for
all um skin types if you if you have a
dry skin and you're watching this and
you want to try this out please try it
by all means you know try it by all
means I give it 100 out of 100 I give it
10 out of 10 chef's kiss my
baby literally I love love love love
these products um yeah man so those were
the products these are all the products
I will hold them like this yay Leiva is
the way to go guys I promise so so I
advise
you to try the
small box the small package Fest and if
you're happy with the results you can go
for other fulls sized products of a
bigger range um I'm I'm excited guys
like my skin is really really really
really loving these products really
loving these products and if you've been
watching my skin care product um videos
you will know that I was struggling from
hyperpigmentation I tried so many
products that did not work you know and
I ended up
using userin which really kicked off my
um my healing process my healing process
from hyperpigmentation it really did and
then I was like because I love reviewing
um skin care products let me try Le and
I loved it and and now I'm using liiv
and I recommend it 10 out of 10 100 out
of 100 chef's kiss Thank you so much for
watching if you've watched until this
far please like please comment and
please
subscribe I'll see you in another video
thank you guys bye
[Music]